<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GuiaTour</string>
    <string name="generic_error_message">Não foi possível buscar</string>
    <string name="long_text_for_tests">Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. Loren ipsum text for the sake of the example to make the scrollable content longer than the screen height. </string>
</resources>